

Date of birth: September 5, 1984 Language: Persian (Native), English Grade: Male Marital Status: Married Country of citizenship: Iran Phone (+98-28) 33686323

Mobile: (+98) 9122819015 (WhatsApp)

E-mail:

MJ.Namazifar@gmail.com MJ.Namazifar@yahoo.com

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/mj-namazifar

Skype live: @Namazifar

≜: https://namazifar.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Hackerrank.com Codewars.com Stackoverflow.com

Mohammad Javad Namazifar

Objective

I'm interested in computer science, software engineering, artificial intelligence and robotics. With +9 year experience as .NET developer using C#, Experienced with relational database in Microsoft SQL Server database, design & T-SQL. debugging and problem-solving in order to provide proper solutions. I am very interested in sharing my expertise and motivation with your developing team. A few of my obvious features that can be useful in advancing your organizational goals are the spirit of teamwork and my problem solving ability. I am interested in working in an environment where my expectations are far more than my level of knowledge and skill, and this is a serious stimulus for my personal growth.

Work Experience

1- BIG¹, IT-Designer and developer [Aug 2020 - Present]

URL: http://www.Polfilm.net/

POLFILM is the first and largest leading manufacturer of BOPP films in Iran. I am currently working as a senior software engineer in the IT department of Bayazian Industrial Group. During my stay in this company, I designed and implemented the following fields:

- Sales and Marketing ASP.NET Core MVC and Database MSSQL Server
- Production Planning Control (PPC) Plate, Polfilm, Petco and Atlasfilm company, C# WinForms and Database MSSQL Server
- Implemented Processes and Services provided by the IT department in the software platform (ITIL²) at Plate, Polfilm, Petco, Atlasfilm, Atlas Boobin and PayKaran company.
- Designed a Dbsyncer Synchronize distributed databases to integrate data into a single database based on scheduler, *C# WCF and Database MSSQL Server*
- Implemented REST APIs with ASP.NET Core MVC and Database MSSQL Server, for the provide services to other enterprise applications, based JWT token based authentication
- Analyze and integrate multiple heterogeneous data sources across the company using MS SQL Server, SSIS

Achievement:

Web development, ITIL, WCF, good knowledge of Integrate and Db syncing

Learning:

· REST APIs, SSIS

Tech stack: WCF/MSSQL/ SSIS

¹ Baiazian Industrial Group

² Information Technology Infrastructure Library

2- Arta Company, Senior Software Engineer [Jun 2019 - Sep 2020]

TAMASHACHI website belongs to Arta company. The company informs users about the news and results of live sports such as football. I worked part-time in Arta company for more than a year, during my stay in this company, I designed and implemented the following fields:

- Implemented REST APIs with ASP.NET Core MVC and Database MSSQL Server, Back-end Website Online results of football sports events, https://tamashachi.com
- API Football Analysis
- Designing a database for football data, teams, players, events and etc.
- Implementing a Back-end synchronize database with Football data server
- Serving in Persian and English language to the website and mobile App
- Implementing a dashboard to test the services provided, based on swagger

Achievement:

• experience a real team work, Commitment to work and deadlines

Learning:

• Walk through real development ASP.Net Core

Tech stack: ASP.Net Core/ MSSQL / JSON/

3- SDC¹, IT-Designer and developer [Jul 2013 - Aug 2020]

URL: http://www.seven-diamonds.com

I worked for more than 7 years in the IT department of Seven Diamonds Industrial company which is in the field of steel industry, during this time, I worked on the following fields:

- Management Information System(MIS), C# and Database Programming
- Microsoft Dynamics AX (ERP)
 - o Installing and configuring of the Dynamics AX 2012 R2/R3 ERP
 - Workflow configuration and setup
 - o Users and Role management
 - Procurement and sourcing
 - o Product and Procurement Catalog / Policy Rules
 - o Procedures and processes of Procurement, Quality Control, Warehouse
 - o Product and Service information management
 - Procedures and Production Control Processes
- Design and implementation of Processes and Services provided by the IT department in the software platform (ITIL)
 - User Panel for End user to track and report problems
 - Incident Management
 - o Service/Incident Catalog
 - Business Rules (organize all the incoming requests and perform actions such as delivering them to IT groups)
 - Automatic Request Distribution
 - Service Level Agreement (SLA)
 - Asset Management
 - o User Survey
- Content management system, SharePoint 2016
- Design and implementation of Stop monitoring software related production lines
 - Lessening and receiving information about stop-of-production lines from control boards in the parallel port
 - Insert information about the stops and start-up of production lines in the database
 - Data mining and reporting on duration time stop the production lines
- Implementation of software amortized costs of company units on production lines, to calculate the cost of goods
 - o Receive information on costs of production and non-production centers
 - The formation of a multiplex table, based on the financial and industrial accounting period

_

¹ Seven Diamonds Company – Steel Alborz Company

- Calculated and amortized the costs to the manufacturing centers
- Seven-Diamonds Company Website
 - o Design concepts and contents according to functional requirement company
 - Implement responsive multilingual WordPress website mock-up into fully functioning websites employing HTML, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery and Bootstrap
- Quality defect detection Steel Products Seven Diamonds Industry using Machine Learning and Image Processing
 - Collecting images of product quality defects
 - Classification of product's quality defects by *OpenCV* and machine learning algorithms

Achievement:

• Getting good knowledge of development in ERP

Learning:

 MS Dynamics AX 2012, ITIL, WordPress, Walk through real development in .Net and C#, Stored Procedures

Tech stack: MS Dynamics AX | MSSQL | Deep Learning|

Research Experience

1- MRL¹, MRL, @Home Robot Team [JUL 2012 – JAN 2014]

I was with MRL @home team at Azad University of Qazvin, Department of Electronics, Computer and Information Technology Engineering From 2012 to 2014 as a researcher with interests in

- Human-Robot Interaction (HRI)
- Target Tracking
- Human-Following Mobile Robot
- Laser and Vision-based Tracking Multiple Moving Targets with a Mobile Robot
- Sensor and Classifier Fusion for Fast Human Detection
- Detection of Human Pairs of Legs using a 2D Laser Range Finder(LRF)

2- AUT², Algorithm and Computational Geometry Laboratory [DEC 2011 – FEB 2013]

I was with Algorithm and Computational Geometry Laboratory Amirkabir University, Tehran, Iran, Department of Computer From 2011 to 2013 as a researcher with interests in

- Watchman Route Problem (WRP)
- Freeze Tag Problem (FTP)
- Swarm Robotic
- Heuristic and Meta-Heuristic Algorithm

3- MRL³, Rescue Robot Team [DEC 2007 – JAN 2012]

I was a member of Rescue robot RoboCup team at Azad University of Qazvin, Department of Electronics, Computer and Information Technology Engineering From 2007 to 2012 during which I have experienced in these fields:

- Customize kernel Linux OS for Embedded PC
- Developing an embedded Linux operating system for robots
- Autonomous robot exploration in unknown environments
- Victim Detection
- Merge 2d laser Map
- Sensors Robot Stabilizing with PID controller

Teaching Experience

Instructor at Islamic Azad University Oazvin, Department of Computer & IT Engineering [2012–2014]

Course: Operating System, Computer Workshop

¹ Mechatronics Research Laboratory, Azad University of Qazvin, Iran

² Amirkabir University Tehran, Department of Computer and Information Technology Engineering

³ Mechatronics Research Laboratory, Azad University of Qazvin, Iran

Education

- M.Sc. in Computer Engineering (Software) *Electronics, Computer and IT Engineering Department*, Islamic Azad University, Qazvin Branch, Iran [Fall 2010 2013]
 - o Thesis: Presenting Algorithms for Waking up a Swarm of Robots with Radial approach
 - o **Supervisor:** Dr.Alireza Bagheri and Dr.Keivan Borna
- **B.Sc.** in Computer Engineering (Software) *Electronics, Computer and IT Engineering Department*, Islamic Azad University, Qazvin Branch, Iran [Fall 2006 2009]
 - **Project:** Multiplayer game and chat in Mobile device based on the Bluetooth
 - Supervisor: Dr.Behrouz Masoumi

Membership and Professional Experience

- Member of *Talent in Understanding Young Researchers and elite Club*, Islamic Azad University, Iran [2008 Present]
 Link: My page in BPJ
- Member of Technical Committee (TC), *International Iran Open RoboCup Competition*, *Tehran*, *Iran* @Home League [2013 2013]
- Member of Technical Committee (TC), *International Iran Open RoboCup Competition*, *Tehran*, *Iran* Rescue Real League [2015 2015]

Interests and activities

• ERP, ITIL, Integrate multiple heterogeneous data sources, Web Developing

Patents and publications

- 1- F. Barazandeh, M. Norouzi, M. Yaghobi, M. Moshfeghi, M.J.Namazifar, M. Ghaffari Jadidi, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, J.Chegini, J.Zolghadr, M.Rahmani, M.R.Siboni, M.Namazifar, M.Jadaliha, S.M. Mavaei, B. Asadi, M. Farahbakhsh "RoboCupRescue 2008 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2008
- 2- A.M.Shahri, M.Norouzi, M.Yaghobi, S.M.Mavaei, M.J.Namazifar, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, J.Chegini, M.Rahmani, M.Namazifar, B.Asadi "RoboCupRescue 2009 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2009
- 3- A.M.Shahri, J.Chegini, **M.J.Namazifar**, H.montazerzohur, B.MehdiKhani, M.karimi, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, V.Azizi "*RoboCupRescue 2010 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description*", 2010
- 4- A.M.Shahri, J.Chegini, **M.J.Namazifar**, B.MehdiKhani, E.Saeidi, M.Salehzadeh, A.R.HajMohammadhosseini, A.Karambakhsh, A.H.Mashat, M.Rahmani, M.E.Mashat, V.Azizi "RoboCupRescue 2011 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2011
- 5- F.Mahmoudi, V.Mokhtari Hassanabad, F.Maroofkhani, **MJ.Namazifar**, AA.Pasdar, A.Hosseini, F.Abdollahi, F.Abazari, N.Nabavi, MR.Kakvand and A.Shabani Asl. "*RoboCup @Home 2012 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description*", 2012
- 6- F.Mahmoudi, R.Fathzadeh, A.Hosseini, M.J.Namazifar, N.Nabavi, F.Abdollahi, M.Iranikhah, S.Bayani, F.Abazari, R.shahabian and H.Bagher "RoboCup @Home 2013 Robot League Team, RoboCup Team Description", 2013
- 7- MJ.Namazifar, ar.Bagheri, k.Borna"An approximation algorithm for the awakening of robots in Euclidean space" *National Conference on Science, Engineering, New Ideas (8), Tonekabon, Branch future institutions of higher learning.* 2014 (in Persian)
- 8- **MJ.Namazifar**, A.Bagheri, K.Borna, "Linear time constant factor approximation algorithm for the Euclidean `Freeze-Tag` robot ", Advances in Computer Science: an International Journal, 2015.

Certificates & Awards received

- Presenting a plan entitled "Create Intelligent Autonomy in Rescue Mobile Robot", Fajr International Invention & Innovations Exhibition (FINEX 2008), Tehran, Iran. [February 2008].
- Being exempted from master's program entrance examination as an "Exceptional Talented" student in Qazvin Islamic Azad University, 2009.
- **Scholarship** of Azad University, Qazvin Branch [2006-2013].
- Certification training course "Principles of Supervision" Qazvin University Jahad, 2016.
- Certification training course "Process Management and Modeling Process with BPMN Focus", 2017.
- @Home Robot League:
 - o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup @Home in Iran, 2012.

o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup @Home in Iran, 2013.

• Rescue Real Robot League:

- o 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot League, **Turkey** 2011.
- o 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot **Best Autonomy** Challenge, **Turkey** 2011.
- o 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot **Manipulation Challenge**, **Turkey** 2011.
- o 3rd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot League, **Austria** 2009.
- Best Autonomy Robot in International Thailand Rescue Robot Competition, 2008.
- o 3rd Place in **Thailand** Rescue Robot Competition, 2008.
- o 1st Place in **Khwarizmi** Robotic competition, Iran 2008.
- o 2nd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot League, **China** 2008.
- o 3rd Place in RoboCup Rescue Robot **League Locomotion Challenge** (*Best in Class Mobility*), **China** 2008.
- Award of Technical Challenge in **Best Mapping Algorithm** at International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real, 2008.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2008.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2009.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2010.
- o 1st Place in International IranOpen RoboCup Rescue Real in Iran, 2011.

Projects

Qt Cross Compile for beagle Bone Black, Micro Alborz System Company [July 2015]

Setting up and configuration Qt and toolchain for cross-compiling

- Cross-Compiling Qt for Beagle board ARM based targets and board bring up using Angstrom/Debian Linux
- o Setting up remote Debugging embedded software based on Otcreator
- o Setting up Linux Device Driver Serial RS232/486

Skills

Programming

- C/C++, JAVA, Python in Linux and Windows
- C#, Pascal, Delphi, Visual Basic, Borland C++, Visual C++, x86 Assembly, Prolog
- Shell Programming in Linux and Windows
- Web Programming ASP .NET Core MVC, HTML, JavaScript,Css, XML,JSON, Caml Technique
- SQL and NoSQL database
- WordPress, SharePoint, SharePoint Designer, InfoPath Designer
- Java Mobile Programming
- Low level Programming, Network Programming
 - Socket Programming TCP/UDP and RTSP / RTP
 - o Implementing CRC
 - o Implementing XML based communication protocol

Packages/Libraries

- Qt Programming in Windows and Linux
- J2me Programming for Cell Phone
- Familiar with OpenGL programming
- Graphics Programming with OpenGL, GlScene
- Cross-Compiler Toolchain
- OpenCV / Deep Learning

Data Bases

MS SQL Server, MS Access, MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB

Robotics Packages

• ROS (Robot Operating System)

Hardware Integration/Programming

• Hokuyo Laser Range Finders (LRF), XSens MTi, Embedded Industrial IBM Compatible, Pan-tilt CMUcam, Beagle Bone Board (BBB), Dynamixel RX-64

Operating Systems

- MS Dos, Windows (Most Versions), Linux (Fedora, OpenSUSE, Ubuntu, Tiny OS, SliTaz)
- Customize Kernel Linux, Embedded Linux Developing

ERP

• Microsoft Dynamics AX 2009, 2012 R2, 2012 R3

Project Management

• SVN, Git in Linux and Windows

• Agile/Scrum

References

Hossein Nazari: <u>h.nazari@seven-diamonds.com</u>

Dr. Alireza M.Shahri: shahri@iust.ac.ir

Dr. Mohammad Norouzi: mh.norouzi@gmail.com

Hobbies

• Soccer, Music, Sudoku, Watching documentary

Graduate Courses

I had some studies on graduate courses such as

- Advanced Operating System and Distributed Operating System
- Advanced Database and Distributed Database
- Parallel Processing Algorithms
- Advance Computer Graphics
- Computational Geometry
- Multi Agent Systems
- Data Compression

Last updated: October 12, 2021